# OJELADE **OLUWASEGUN**

#### ARCHITECTURAL DESIGER

 P Ogba, Lagos State. | ● 070 8132 5288, 070 6482 7731 | ● info.ojelad@gmail.comgmail.com

## SKILLS

7+ Years of Experience

AutoCAD SketchUp Adobe Photoshop V-ray Render

5+ Years of Experience

Lumion

2+ Years of Experience

Revit Architecture Adobe Premier Pro

0-1 Year of Experience

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Indesign

## **EDUCATION**

HND, Architecture Moshood Abiola Polytechnic 2017 - 2019

OND, Architecture Moshood Abiola Polytechnic 2014 - 2016

## ACTIVITIES/ HOBBIES

Videography Photography

Model making

Gaming Tennis Music listening

## REFERENCES

Available on request.

#### PROFILE

I am a resourceful team player and a result-driven with a keen eye for detail and a deep passion for creating structures that meet client's expectations. I am committed to utilizing my skills and experience to enhance the organization's performance by increasing efficiency, improving productivity and maximizing profitability.

## EXPERIENCE

Architect & Designer | Segun Oriola Associate

2022 - Present

- Responsible for producing detail drawings that provide precise technical specifications for various aspect of building design.
- Collaborated with other professionals on the architectural team to ensure that the drawings accurately represented the intended design and met all necessary safety and functional requirements.

Clerk of Work | Works and Service Department, College of Education, Akamkpa, Cross River State.

2021 - 2022 (NYSC)

- Regular inspection on workmanship and quality of work on construction site
- Conducting regular site inspection to ensur building plans are followed correctly.
- produced few detail drawings.

## Architect & Designer | Archroute limited

2019 - 2021

- Produced Architectural presentaion and working drawings
- Collaborated with other professionals on the architectural team to ensure that the draings accurately represented the intended design and met all necessary safety and functional requirements.

Office Assistant Intern | Ministry of Housing, Alausa, Ikeja, Lagos State.

2016 - 2017

- Participated in the preparation of Architectural working drawings.
- Participated in regular site site inspection
- Drafting and filling of progress report on visited construction sites.